CHARLES WEFSO

FRONTEND SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Bio

I became a software engineer so that I could use my creativity and problem solving abilities to improve lives in meaningful ways. I have a background as a writer, a deep love of learning, and a passion for working collaboratively to develop useful and intuitive experiences.

Work History

Clerk (https://clerk.com/) Dec 2021 - Oct 2023

Clerk is an authentication and user management tool that allows developers to add full user features to their app in minutes. I was a Frontend Engineer on the marketing team, working with designers to create our primary web page. I also worked as a Support Engineer, helping users fix bugs and integrate Clerk into their applications.

Used technologies:

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React, NextJS, Sanity CMS, Tailwind, ChakraUI, Cypress and many other third party integrations.

ReRent (https://www.join.rerent.co/) Jan 2021 - Dec 2023

ReRent is a small startup focused on helping students and other short-term renters manage their properties. I was involved in building this app from the ground up, working on both the marketing materials, as well as the functionality of the app itself.

Used technologies:

Front End: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Jest, GraphQL

Education

Turing School of Software and Design Front End Curriculum

March 2020 - September 2020

Turing is an intensive 7 month program which focuses on the practical development of software applications. We were required to deliver MVPs on a weekly basis, and to constantly research and apply new technologies and frameworks to our projects.

More Info

Location Denver, CO

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/charles-wefso/

Phone 605-787-3034

Email cwefso@gmail.com